顶峰
娱 乐 公 司
钻石中心
收  购 黄金 钻石
罗斯福酒店
- 我姓沃克 - 好的
- Last name's Walker. - Yes.
沃克先生
Mr. Walker.
南阁的2015房间 视野开阔的房间
Room 2105, South Tower. Great view.
现在东阁还有一间更大的房间
We also have a larger unit available on the east side
我们可以按原价提供给您
I can offer you at the same price.
不用 我就要这间
No, I think I'll stick with the view.
现在喝香槟是不是有点早
Is it too early for champagne?
不会啊 先生 一点也不早
Not at all, sir. Not at all.
我的天哪 看那
Look! There's a man up there!
快看 就在那儿
Look! Right there!
- 哪儿 - 就那儿
- Where? - Right there!
快打911报警啊
Somebody call 911!
纽约州新新监狱
一个月前
打他 打得好 把他打趴下
Hit him! That's right, take him down!
所有犯人...
All inmates...
你的最后上诉被否决了 卡西迪先生
So your final appeal has been denied, Mr. Cassidy.
我特意来告诉你的
That's why I am here.
浪费时间 我能走了吗 嗯
It's a waste of time. Can I go? Mmm-hmm?
你的人生结束了
Your old life is over.
你必须坦然接受 没有挽回的余地了
You're gonna have to accept that it's never coming back.
人们很难理解一个警察 为什么会被判25年的有期徒刑
Not many men, let alone an ex-cop, can handle a 25-year sentence.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
尼克 你曾经想过自杀吗
Nick, have you ever considered hurting yourself?
- 自杀 - 嗯
- Hurting? - Mmm-hmm.
没有
No.
但我想过杀人
But killing,
每天他妈的都想
every goddamned day.
确认自己
口袋是空的
*空  的*
带他进去
Go ahead.
嗨 卡斯
Hey, Cass.
有些日子没见了
It's been a while.
是啊
Yes, it has.
- 麦克 这是新买的吗 - 是的
- That's new, Mike. - Yeah.
我去购物了
I went shopping.
我马上就要结婚了 所以必须把自己打理干净点
I'm about to be a married man, so gotta clean up a little bit.
哪个男人这么幸运
Who's the lucky guy?
嘿 你知道 生活总是要继续的 对吧
You know, man. Hey, life goes on, right?
是啊
Yeah.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
- 为什么 - 不是指这个
- Go on. - No, we gotta flip this.
我是说 我们必须翻案 我们必须寻找一些新的证据 我觉得我们能做到 你明白吗
I mean, we dig up some new evidence. There's things we can do. You know?
没事的
It's okay.
这不允许接吻
No kissing.
你弟弟给我打电话了
Your brother called.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
他想要什么 又是要钱吗
What'd he want? He ask for money again?
是关于你爸爸
It's your dad.
- 嗯 - 他...
- Yeah? - He's...
他快不行了
He's dying.
- 多长时间了 - 不久前
- How long? - Soon.
我会向狱长求情
Look, I'll talk to the warden.
让你出狱一天 不要惹麻烦
I'll get you a day outside of here. No hassles.
- 好的 - 行吧
- Mmm. - All right?
自己多保重
Take care of yourself.
嗯
Yep.
当善良的灵魂离我们而去 我们必定难以接受
And when a good soul is taken from us, it's hard to find reason to believe.
但我们必须坚信神的许诺 相信自己
But having faith in God's promise, and faith in yourself,
方可助你走出悲痛
is your one true ally.
愿上帝保佑你 弗兰克·卡西迪 你已完全自由
God bless you, Frank Cassidy. You are truly free.
阿门
Amen.
- 阿门 - 谢谢你们
- Amen. - Thank you.
- 谢谢您 神父 - 节哀顺便
- Thank you, Father. - I'm so sorry.
嘿 卡斯 兄弟 别太难过
Hey, Cass. I'm sorry, man.
很高兴见到你 尼克
It's nice to meet you, Nick.
我也是
Likewise.
有什么我能做的 就告诉我
Anything I can do, just let me know.
我一定帮你到底 好吗
I'll be there, okay?
好的
Yeah.
老兄 不能接触
Ma'am! No contact!
嘿 美女可以破个例
Hey. Pretty girls can break the rules.
- 嗯 待会儿见 - 待会儿见 宝贝
- Okay, I'll see you. - I'll see ya, babe.
你竭尽全力了是吗
Is this the best you could do?
你和那些该死的药真他妈没用
View of the goddamned tracks?
喂 你进监狱的那天就把爸爸害死了
You killed him the day you went to prison.
因为我把爸爸留给了一个废物赡养
That's 'cause I left him with a screw-up.
哦 是吗 尼克 你不在我们也过的挺好
Oh, yeah? You know, Nick, we're doing real good without you.
是啊 看看现在
Yeah, looks like it.
- 嘿 你俩住手 - 住手 快点 站起来
- Hey! Break it up, you two! - Break it up! Come on. Get up!
滚回监狱里去
Get your ass back to prison!
别碰我 走开
Get off me! Get away!
- 好了 冷静点 - 冷静...
- All right. Calm down. - Calm...
趴下 趴下 把枪放下
Down! Down! Put your gun down!
- 时间到了 - 放下
- Time's up! - Down!
你到底在做什么
The hell are you doing?
把枪放下 约翰尼 别忘了 你还有两个孩子
Put the gun down! You got two kids, Donnie. Think about it.
好的 别冲动 尼克
All right. Take it easy, Nick.
现在 待在原地 你也是
Now get down and sit on your hands! You, too.
嘿 乔伊 拿钥匙
Hey, Joey. Keys.
- 你疯了吗 - 钥匙
- Have you lost your mind? - Keys!
- 在警察身上 - 快点
- On the belt. - Hurry!
你最好别回来了
You better not come back here.
当然 我没打算回来
Yeah, I didn't plan to.
乔伊 很对不住你们两个 跪下
I'm sorry, but you, too, Joey. Get down!
都不许动
Nobody move.
你这样会让爸爸自豪
Way to make Dad proud!
我是编号3-12 犯人逃跑了
This is 3-12, prisoner escape!
全体支援 派人堵住东边出口
All backup units, prisoner's heading to the east gate!
快叫救护车 快点
Get a paramedic out here, now!
- 你看见了他吗 - 我什么都看不见了
- See him? - I can't see anything.
- 检查后座 - 看看后座
- Check the back. - Look in the back.
到底发生了什么事
What the hell happened?
他袭击了警察还抢了我的车
He jacked the guards and took my car.
天哪
Jesus.
他是个重罪逃犯 麦克 他们会杀了他的
He's an escaped felon, Mikey. They're gonna kill him.
快看 上边有人
Look! There's a man up there!
- 快看 就在那儿 - 哪儿
- Look! Right there! - Where?
有个男人站在窗台上
We got a guy on the roof.
罗斯福区需要紧急事务小组支援 麦迪逊45号
I need an Emergency Service Unit at the Roosevelt, 45th and Madison.
封锁街区 有个男人要跳楼
Shut down the block. We got a man on a ledge.
让开 让开
Back up! Back up!
5号街和麦迪逊大道之间的45号街已经封锁
45th Street, between 5th and Madison, is closed.
- 你怎么看 约翰 - 你怎样
What do you say, John? - How are ya?
开玩笑的吧
You gotta be kidding me.
- 肯定会一塌糊涂 - 哦 是啊
- That'll make a mess. - Oh, yeah.
不准过人 不准过车
No pedestrians. No vehicles.
- 请求救生垫 - 送救生垫过去
- Call for the bag. - Bring the bag.
- 走开 - 嗨 沃克先生 请冷静点
- Just get away. - All right, Mr. Walker. Stay calm.
我叫杰克·多尔蒂 我是来帮你的
My name is Jack Dougherty. I'm here to help.
- 把这车停好 - 是 长官
- Park my vehicle. - Yes, sir.
- 我要在这流动指挥 - 马上照办
- I want mobile command here pronto. - Right away.
- 把这辆油罐车移走 - 好的
- Get this gas truck out of here. - Okay.
持续封锁街区 确保酒店周围安全
Get the street locked up. Businesses, too.
以防他跳下时砸到人
I don't want this guy falling on someone's head.
让这些人后退 我们必须把他们撤离现场
Get all these people back. We gotta move 'em back farther.
行动吧 快点
Let's do it. Come on.
多尔蒂 汇报情况
Dougherty, report.
好了 抓牢点
All right. Hang tight.
我在21楼
Yeah, 21st floor.
跳楼者30岁左右 看起来有点难办了
Jumper's mid-30$, looks like a professional type.
- 他拒绝交谈 - 知道了
- And he's not talking. - Got it.
我是马库斯警官
Detective Marcus.
听着 我需要了解情况 任何和他稍微接触过的人
Listen, I need to talk to anyone on your staff that had any sort of contact with him.
旅馆服务员 职员 查清所有人 懂吗
Bellhops, clerks, anybody, okay?
好的 警官
Yes, sir.
别跳啊 哥们
Don't do it, man!
沃克先生
Mr. Walker...
我要见个女人
I want a woman.
没问题 听着 如果就这些的话 你看咱们进来谈如何
All right, look. If that's what this is about, what do you say we come inside,
我们会满足你所有的要求 金发美女 浅黑肤色的女人 如你所愿
we'll take care of whatever you need. Blonde? Brunette? You name it.
我要见丽迪雅·默瑟探员
Detective Lydia Mercer.
如果她三十分钟内不出现 我就跳下去 你明白吗
If she's not here in 30 minutes, then I jump. Do you understand?
- 我会考虑你的要求 - 那我的话就说完了 杰克
- I'll look into it. - Then I guess we're done talking, Jack.
真不敢相信
You're not gonna believe this.
- 他想见默瑟 - 什么
- Wants Mercer. - What?
他说如果我们不叫她来 他就跳下去
He says if we don't get her, he's going off.
他这是要最后一次开荤吗
His "Last Supper"?
不是什么好兆头 看看这个
Not a good sign. And take a look at this.
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
纽约罗斯福酒店
我将离开这个世界
就像我来时一样
清清白白
是啊 我们可能要把他送到精神病院
Yeah. More likely he's going to the nuthouse.
好的 把指纹鉴证科的人叫来 我会申请查明他的身份
All right. I want the print guys up here. Get an ID.
给默瑟打电话
And call Mercer.
什么 你开玩笑吗 你是认真的
What? Are you kidding me? Seriously?
到时候你援助她 你是我的人
You'll back her up. You're my guy.
好的 为什么不呢 每个人都喜欢扫把星 不是吗
Sure, why not? Everybody loves a good train wreck, right?
该死
Shit.
什么事
Yeah?
天啊 默瑟 我吵醒你了吗
Jesus Christ, Mercer, did I wake you up?
当然没有 等一下 别挂了
Of course not. Hang on. Just hang on a sec.
你开玩笑吗 事情很急
Are you kidding me? We don't have time for this.
默瑟
Mercer?
好了 什么事
All right, what?
有人跳楼 你赶紧过去
We got a jumper, and you're up.
- 不行 我正在休假 - 不用多说
- No, I'm not on the rotation. - No shit.
罗斯福酒店21楼 立刻过去
The Roosevelt Hotel. 21st floor. Right now.
噢 该死
Oh, crap.
收到 我们已经和交通管制部门 管辖区和酒店取得联系
Roger that. We've got links with traffic control, the precinct, and the hotel.
把监控打开 查到J·沃克的消息吗
Get the cameras up. Anything on J. Walker?
这个城市就有超过600个叫沃克的
We've got over 600 of 'em in the city.
去查查吧
Go figure.
- 消防队长请求指示 - 知道了
- The Fire Chief wants a word. - Got it.
好像有什么事发生了 咱们去看看 从这儿走
It looks like we're in for a show. Let's get it. Right over here.
咱们从他转弯的地方走 准备好了吗
Let's go from where he swerves around. Ready?
我看着还行吗
Is my hair okay?
美丽动人
Gorgeous.
别嘲笑我 保罗
Don't fluff me, Paul.
三 二 一...
Three, two, one.
突发新闻
现场直播
市中心交通大堵塞
情场失意 股市低迷的受害者
Unlucky in love? Victim of the stock market?
一个年轻的男人正欲轻生
A young man contemplates death.
我是苏西·莫哈里斯 这是从市中心发来的报道
This is Suzie Morales reporting live from Midtown.
把救生垫一直扯到墙角 明白吗
Stretch it full down to the corners, all right?
好的 明白
All right, got it.
噢 天哪
Oh, man.
他要是掉到这上边就运气十足了
Good luck hitting this.
- 别推我 伙计 - 嘿 往后退
- Don't shove me, man. - Hey! Back up!
我有权想去哪儿就去哪儿
I got a right to walk where I want.
这儿已经封锁了
All sealed off.
妈的
Shit.
默瑟
Mercer.
- 可以开始工作了吗 - 当然 长官
- You good to work? - Absolutely, sir.
希望如此 上吧
You'd better be. Get to it.
默瑟要上去了
Mercer's on her way up.
死神来了
Enter the Grim Reaper.
默瑟
Mercer.
欢迎回来上班 再次看到你真高兴
Welcome back. It's so good to see you again.
去死吧 杰克
Kiss my ass, Jack.
跟你讲 他点名要见你
FYI, he asked for you. By name.
现场什么情况
What's the scene?
有一张自杀的字条 他叫沃克 但我们从来没见过他
Suicide note. His name is Walker, but we haven't made him yet.
他一直缄口不言 不过他说两分钟后会跳下去
And he's not talking, other than to say he's gonna go off in about two minutes.
两分钟
Two minutes.
- 去见见他 - 2分钟
- Go get him. - Two minutes.
- 他求助了吗 - 没有
- He ask for help? - No.
- 喝多了 - 看着不像
- Drunk? - He doesn't appear to be.
- 戴着结婚戒指吗 - 没有
- Wedding ring? - Nope.
- 提了什么要求 - 就想一睹你的芳颜
- Demands? - Just to see your pretty face.
还剩1分钟
One minute!
给我杯咖啡 求你了 给我杯咖啡吧
Coffee? Please. Don't make me beg.
马上给你送来 不过你已经没时间享受了
You got it. But time is a-wastin'.
- 你们检查了这个吗 - 查过了
- Have you processed these yet? - Yeah.
昨夜很颓废 是吧
Another rough night, huh?
还剩十秒
10 seconds!
上吧 没时间了
Let's go. Tick-took.
五
Five!
四
Four!
三
Three!
- 二 - 沃克先生
- Two! - Mr. Walker?
我是丽迪雅·默瑟探员 我知道你现在需要我
I'm Detective Lydia Mercer. I understand you asked for me.
你爬出窗台是为了什么呢
What brings you out here today?
这儿风景不错
Aside from the view?
相信我 从高处看深渊的感觉...
Trust me, this staring off into the abyss stuff...
可不怎么好
It's no good.
从今天以后 我的生活将会永远的改变
Today is the day that everything changes.
非好即坏
One way or another.
什么会变呢
What's gonna change?
我已经做好死的准备
I'm ready to die.
重要的是你能不能理解我
It's important to me that you understand that.
我理解你
I understand.
哦 那好
Oh, yeah.
为什么选我 沃克先生
Why me, Mr. Walker?
嗯
Hmm?
若你真准备自杀的话 为什么要我来呢
If you're really ready to die, why'd you bring me up here?
你很出名
You're famous.
上个月在桥上 你和想跳下去的人谈判
Last month you were with a jumper on a bridge,
然后他在全世界关注下跳桥自杀
and he died with the whole world watching.
我只是想跳下去以后 周围有很多人围观而已
I just wanted to know that I could get a good crowd for when I go off.
哦
Wow.
干得不错 令人印象深刻
Really nice work. Very impressive.
我见你们很谈得来 真不错
I saw the connection you guys made. It was nice.
- 让房间里的人都出去 - 我哪儿也不去
- Clear the room. - I'm not going anywhere.
这儿是我的地盘 我做主 出去
My scene. My room. Get out.
伙计们 听到了 咱们走吧
You heard her, guys. Let's go.
这样能让你保持冷静 干得不错
Way to keep your cool. Nicely done.
给你五分钟时间搞定
I'll give you five minutes.
店主们都在抱怨妨碍生意
We're getting a lot of static from the store owners.
我担心这个 叫他们维持人群秩序 好吧 别老拿这些蛋疼的事烦我
Do I care? I mean, get more crowd control, all right. Don't break my balls about this.
街道保持封锁 直到我认为安全为止
The street stays closed till I say it's safe.
你有亲戚朋友吗 要我联系他们吗
You got any friends or family you want me to call for you?
没有
No.
我父亲去世了
My father's dead.
所以你就要跳楼吗
Is that why you're out here?
差不多
In a way.
想谈谈你父亲吗
Do you want to talk about it?
你知道 干你们这行的...
You know, this job of yours...
确实很辛苦 不是份美差
It's a pretty grim way to make a living.
我比较喜欢把注意力放在需要帮助的人身上
I prefer to focus on the people I help.
我希望你就是其中之一
I'm hoping you're one of 'em.
你在警队里有很多朋友
You got a lot of friends on the force?
够多了
Enough.
我敢打赌你在男人圈子里不怎么受欢迎
I bet you're not too popular with the boys' club.
是 是他 没错
Yeah, it's him. No doubt.
- 肯尼迪国际机场那边有消息吗 - 没
- Anything at JFK? - No.
那边境呢
Anything at the borders?
没有 他不会犯这种低级错误
No, he's not gonna make a mistake like that.
- 汤姆 听我说 - 嗯 怎么了
- Tom, listen. - Yeah, what?
我想让你查下他所有的电话和信用卡记录
I want you to look through all the cell phone and credit card records.
是尼克和乔伊·卡西迪
Nick and Joey Cassidy.
好的 没问题
Okay. Right.
有什么异常情况 及时向我汇报
Anything reoccurring, anything unusual. You run it through me.
好的
All right.
第一个向我报告
I want to find him first.
我倒希望你能一直戴着手套
I'd sure appreciate it if you kept the gloves on.
5分钟时间已经到了 是吧
Five minutes up already, huh?
我不是问这事 警长 你掩护我 进不进来
I didn't ask for this, Detective. You back me up. Are you in or out?
进或不进 我进
In or out? I'm in.
开始吧 伙计们
Let's go, guys.
我跟你讲 莫妮卡
I'll tell you what, Monica.
说吧 我听着呢
Uh-huh. I'm listening.
我将为金环成员以及他们家人举办一场晚宴
I'll host a dinner for the Gold Circle patrons and their families.
大卫 我不知该说些什么 你真是太大方了
David, I don't know what to say. That would be incredibly generous.
- 嗯 这都是为了孩子们 不是吗 - 对 是啊
- Well, it's for the children's wing, right? - Right. Yeah.
我是说 在这种经济情况下 我还是能帮些忙的
I mean, in this economy, that's the least I could do.
您真伟大 我就知道能靠你
You're a dream. I knew I could count on you
- 当然 - 谢谢
- Yeah. Of course. - Thanks.
好的 再见
Okay. Good. Bye.
老板 亨利先生来了
Mr. Henry is here, sir.
特德 什么事情
What is it, Ted?
有点小麻烦
There's a problem.
- 今天 - 计划委员会那边已经搞定了
- Not today there isn't. - I've taken care of the planning commission.
但那些议员们
It's the councilman.
若把钱全部划在我户头上的话 风险太大了
It's too much of a risk if they tie that money to me.
听着 我去跟弗兰克谈 看看他能否找到人...
Look. I'll talk to Frank, see if he has someone who can...
大卫 求你了
David, please.
- 这是什么 - 小礼物 真是不好意思
- What's this? - It's a gift. I'm sorry.
哦
Oh.
你知道的 当我第一栋房子卖出去时
You know, when I sold my first building,
银行给了我四个美女 一磅可卡因
the bank sent over four hookers, a pound of cocaine,
然后让我们乘坐他们私人专机去巴黎玩了一圈
and then they flew us all to Paris on their private jet.
那才叫真正的礼物
Now that was a gift.
跟我保证你能办好 泰德 行吗
Tell me it's done, Ted. Hmm?
告诉我你可以搞定
Tell me it's done!
谢谢你的表
Thank you for the watch.
240美元服务 他给了我100美元小费 你说这算啥事
He gave me a $100 tip on a $240 tab. Can you imagine that?
早餐花了240美元
240 bucks for breakfast?
- 一天之内早餐最重要了啊 - 是吗
- It is the most important meal of the day. - Yeah.
你注意到他有什么异常的地方吗
Anything else unusual you noticed?
他的眼睛看上去很诚实
He's got honest eyes.
- 从人的眼神可以看出很多内容 - 我母亲以前常常这么说
- You can tell a lot about a man by his eyes. - My mother used to always say that.
马克 过来下 技术组在这儿没找到任何指纹
Marcus, get this. The techies didn't find a single print.
这里全部查过了吗
They did the whole place?
有点奇怪 你说是不是
A little strange, don't you think?
告诉默瑟
Tell Mercer.
好的 一定照办
Yeah, be my pleasure.
房间检查过了
未发现指纹
嘿 来根烟
Hey. You want a smoke?
不
No.
- 沃克先生... - 怎么
- Mr. Walker... - What?
你现在很绝望无助 我能看出来
I know you're desperate. I can see that.
可我也知道这不是一场普通的自杀
But I also know this isn't a normal suicide.
我不知道出了什么事情
I don't know what's going on here.
但我知道 下面的那群人 他们可不管你死活
But I can tell you, these people down here, they don't care about you.
他们只想看到你跳下去 他们就是来看热闹的
They want you to jump. That's why they're here.
但我关心你的死活
But I do care.
尼克 能听到吗
Nick, can you hear me?
这东西还能用吗
Is this thing working yet?
我想让你告诉我 究竟发生了什么事
And I'm asking you to help me understand what's going on.
我们到了 到了 别害怕
We're here, we're here, we're here. Just don't freak out.
我叫你来 是因为我想找个靠得住的人
I asked for you, because I needed someone I could count on.
信得过的人 因为有可能今天会不大好收场
Someone I could trust, 'cause, chances are, this ain't gonna end well.
你可以不去自杀的 你可以选择活着
It doesn't have to be that way. That's your choice.
我选择 我自己的选择很简单 是吧 跳或者不跳
My choice? My only choice is easy. All right? To jump or not to jump.
- 最终还在于你的选择了 - 我不明白你说什么
- This is gonna come down to your choice. - I don't understand what that means.
你迟到了
You're late!
这里完全水泄不通了 老哥
Midtown's totally grid-locked, bro.
是啊 你是曼哈顿区里唯一个早就知道这点的人
Yeah. And you're the one person in Manhattan who knew it would be.
准备好了吗
You ready?
来吧 咱们走
All right, let's go.
最新消息 我们刚刚得知谈判专家是丽迪雅·默瑟
In breaking news, we have just learned that the negotiating officer is Lydia Mercer.
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
丽迪雅·默瑟
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
- 你开什么玩笑 - 谁都知道 很多人都对她持批评意见
- Are you kidding me with this? - As you may recall, she was widely criticized
- 这都源于她令人质疑的处理方式... - 什么 新闻而已
- for her questionable handling... - What? It's the news.
上个月布鲁克林大桥发生一起惨剧
of last month's tragic incident on the Brooklyn Bridge,
突发新闻
纽约警察局谈判专家到达现场
新人警官自杀
一位年轻的警察在那自杀了
where a young officer lost his life.
- 人们不禁怀疑她是否适合... - 对不起 罗伊 把电视关掉
- One has to wonder about her suitability... - I'm sorry. Roy, turn that off.
我恨这个泼妇
I hate this bitch.
可人们喜欢看名人的事迹 不是吗
Yeah, well, people love a celebrity, right?
自从那件事发生后 我都没睡过好觉
I don't sleep since that happened.
那场景在我脑中一遍遍地重复
It replays over and over in my mind.
我理解 不好意思
I understand. I'm sorry.
没指纹 没姓名 没信用卡记录 谁会这么做啊 多尔蒂
No prints, no name, no credit card. Who does that, Dougherty?
明显是有过案底的人 对吗
Obviously somebody with a history, right?
我去找人来辨认一下嫌疑犯照片吧
Why don't I have the guys go look at some mug shots?
你回去看看电子数据处理
And you get back to the EDP.
股东们已经迟了三十分钟了
The investors are running about 30 minutes behind.
上面有个人想跳楼 导致交通堵塞
There's a jumper on the building and traffic's a mess.
这些人直接拿枪打死自己不就得了
Why don't these people just shoot themselves in the head?
楼顶有个定时锁 你们得在两分钟内赶到
Overnight time locks go down in two minutes.
你能别这么紧张吗
Would you try and relax?
- 一切就绪 - 是吗 一切都已就绪 除了你
- Everything's in place. - Yeah? Everything but you.
安吉 拿着这个
Angie, grab this.
接住
Catch.
你那边如何
How you doing way up there?
嘿 安吉 告诉乔伊别激动 从这儿我能看见他的腿在发抖
Hey, Angie. Tell Joey to relax. I can see his leg shaking from here.
引起这么严重的交通堵塞 那人该被抓起来处决掉
Anyone who creates traffic like this in Midtown should be shot.
我也这么想的 女士
I couldn't agree more, ma'am.
你在想让他赶紧跳了 好给早间新闻作料吗
Are you hoping he jumps in time for the morning shows?
- 不! - 我说他一小时内肯定跳
- No! - I give him an hour.
- 那就赌一把吧 - 50美元
- I'll take the under. - Fifty bucks.
100美元吧 咱们走
Make it $100. Let's go.
嘿 能看见我吗
Hey, you see me?
24小时屋顶维修
别担心
Don't worry.
嗯 看到了
Yeah. I gotcha.
所有人都看着我呢
Everyone's looking at me.
新闻里说你往加拿大跑了
They were saying on the news you're headed for Canada.
现在再好不过了
It couldn't have gone better.
你可以再加点猛料
You could have pulled your punches a little.
是吗 这几年日子可不好过啊
Yeah? It's been a rough couple years.
谁不是啊
Tell me about it.
换频道 等下
Switching comms, hold on.
还剩10秒
Ten seconds.
- 有必要吗 - 8秒
- Really? - Eight.
- 什么 - 7秒
- What? - Seven.
- 现在还抹口红 - 6秒
- You're doing that now? - Six.
5秒 4秒...
Five, four...
系统防护已启用
系统防护正在解除
系统防护已解除
前台 2
大厅 3
防盗门现在应该已经打开了
The night locks should be deactivated.
一切就绪
That's all good.
- 嘿 听着 这是你最后的机会了 - 绝不
- Hey, listen. This is your last chance. - No.
- 你不必和我一起冒险 - 乔伊
- You don't have to do this. - Joey!
不 听着 我这么做都是为了家庭 为了尼克
No, listen. For me it's family, and for Nick.
- 没错 - 但你可以撒手不管
- Yeah. - But you could just walk away.
我们为此计划了一年 能不能别说这些了
We've been planning this for a year. I'm past committed here.
好吧
All right.
再说了 没有我帮忙 你有可能搞砸了
Besides, you'd probably screw this up without me.
别这么说 不会搞砸的
Don't say that. No one's screwing this up.
我知道 我就说说而已 我给你殿后 行吧
I know. I'm just saying. I got your back, all right?
- 准备好了吗 - 嗯
- Ready? - Huh?
- 准备好了吗 - 准备好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
该你表演了 哥们
It's your show, bro.
看看这些人
Look at all these people.
噢 我可不能让他们失望
Oh, can't disappoint them.
- 嘿 你要干嘛 不行 - 3秒...
- Hey, what are you doing? No! - Three...
嘿 看着我
Hey! Look at me!
- 沃克 看着我 - 2秒...
- Walker! Look at me! - Two...
- 1秒 - 别跳
- One! - Don't!
赶紧跳啊 跳完不就完事了
Why don't you jump and get it over with?
- 你还好吗 - 嗯 从来没觉得这么生机勃勃
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I've never felt more alive.
- 你还好吗 - 没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
钢铁般的意志
Nerves of steel.
我想现在最好能抽根烟
Think I might need that cigarette now.
最后一根 一起抽吧
Last one. Do you mind sharing?
我能体会得到那位警察跳下之后 你所承受的痛苦
I can imagine how it must have felt after that cop jumped.
警察们都很迷信
Cops are superstitious.
他们会把你当瘟疫一样 逃得远远的
And they would've run from you like the plague.
你这是经验之谈
Are you speaking from experience?
但你从未退缩
But you never quit.
从来都没
Never.
去年 你进行了整整68个小时的解救人质的谈判
Last year, you did 68 hours straight in a hostage negotiation.
你把所有人都救了出来
You got everyone out.
你相信自己的直觉 你从未退缩 从未放弃
You trusted your instincts. You never quit. You never gave up.
你怎么对我这么了解
Why do you know so much about me?
因为你和我有着许多共同点
Because you and I have a lot in common.
我觉得你不会跳楼
I don't think you wanna jump.
某一刻 你是不是能感觉到
Is there a moment when you can tell
别人是否想跳楼
if someone's gonna go off or not?
你懂的 某些时候可以
Sometimes you know.
有时候你会感觉到他们要放弃
Sometimes you can feel them give up.
别对我放弃希望
Don't give up on me.
我打算把你从窗台边救回来
I'm gonna get you off this ledge.
你什么时候开始抽烟了
Since when do you smoke?
看看能不能提取些信息
See if you can get a partial.
干得不错
Nice work.
嘿 尼克
Hey, Nick.
兄弟 我们进来了
We're in, buddy.
- 5 1... - 5-1-6 两个2 星号键
- Five, one... - 5-1-6, double 2, star.
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
电梯 2
电梯 3
电梯 1
电梯 4
这里是由苏西·莫拉莱斯从市区为您进行的现场报道
This is Suzie Morales reporting live from Midtown.
在这个国家里 每隔17分钟就有人自杀...
Someone in this country commits suicide every 17 minutes...
- 出什么事了 - 有个跳楼的
- What's going on? - Jumper.
肯定是女人把他逼到跳楼了
Bet it's a woman drove him up there.
是钱的问题 女人才为情而跳 男人 我们只为钱而跳
It's money. Women jump for love. Men? We jump for money.
都怪经济崩溃
Fricking economy.
- 现场在哪儿 - 罗斯福酒店
- Where is it? - The Roosevelt.
那是照片吗
Is that a photo?
你老爸的
Of your dad?
是啊
Yeah.
他总是支持我
He always stood by me.
就算没什么道理 他也站在我这边
Even when nothing made sense, he stood by me.
这种人不多见了
People like that are rare.
进来跟我我聊聊你老爸吧 里边安全点
Why don't you come in and tell me about him? Where it's safer.
- 只有我们两个人 - 不行
- Just the two of us. - No.
我不会进去的
That's not gonna happen.
一切都会好起来
Things will get better.
我们准备再靠近点拍
We're just gonna move in for a closer shot.
伙计们 把这直升机赶走
Boys, get this chopper out of here!
尼克 坚持住
Nick! Hold on!
马克 上边出了什么事
Marcus! What's going on up there?
坚持住 坚持住
Hang on! Hang on!
- 他们的把空中的玩意给清了 - 把这直升机赶走
- Clear the goddamned air space! - Get this out of here!
你在耍我吗
Are you kidding me?
窗台上那个男人是谁
Who is the man on the ledge?
究竟是什么使他做出如此绝望的行为
And what drove him to such a desperate act?
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
不过有一件事是肯定的了
Well, there's one thing for sure,
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
神秘的跳楼者
现场直播
突发新闻
那就是他已经吸引了整个城市的注意力
he has captured the attention of the entire city.
下一步 我们打算和一位精神科法医谈谈
For our next segment we are going to talk to a forensic psychiatrist
- 他或许能给我们些提示... - 嗯 汤姆 你查到了什么
- who may be able to shed some light... - Yeah, Tom, what you got?
资料库里有他兄弟的名字
There's a storage unit in the brother's name.
资料库
Storage?
查到地址了吗
You got a location?
你还好吧
Are you all right?
这是想让我相信你吗
You want me to trust you?
- 那不是我们派出来的 对不起 - 你想让他们抓我吗
- That wasn't ours! I'm sorry! - You're gonna have that?
进来吧
Come in!
真希望一会儿用不到那玩意
I really hope I didn't need that.
乔伊 乔伊
Joey? Joey!
把手伸过来 把手伸过来 过来
Just give me your hand. Give me your hand. Come on.
- 你没事吧 - 没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
好了 莫斯 我们还在想什么
So, Mercer, what are we thinking?
- 跳楼的就该这么跳下去 - 确实如此
- Jumpers jump, right? - Exactly.
这家伙有那能耐 可他不会跳的
This guy has that capacity, but he's not going over.
- 有点不对劲 - 我也是这么想 但到底是什么呢
- Something's off. - That's what I'm thinking. But what?
好像他在等着什么事情发生
It's like he's waiting for something.
查查这个人
We need this ID.
好的 我看看能查到些什么
All right. I'll see what I can do.
这里是苏西·莫哈莱斯 从市中心发来的报导
Suzie Morales reporting from Midtown,
现在整座城市的注意力都集中20层楼窗台上
where the eyes of the city are riveted on a ledge 20 stories up
这个身份不明男子的身上...
and the unidentified man...
- 跳啊 - 他要跳了吗
- Go on! - Is he gonna jump?
- 继续啊 - 跳啊
- Go on! - Jump!
- 跳 跳 跳 - 跳
- Jump! Jump! Jump! - Jump!
- 跳 跳 - 就是 跳啊
- Jump! Jump! - Yeah, jump!
- 你还等什么 - 要跳就跳 别占着茅坑不拉屎
- Get on with it already! - Shit or get off the pot!
不得不喜欢纽约了
Gotta love New York.
或许是时候告诉我 这葫芦里究竟卖的什么药了吧
Maybe it's time you told me what's really going on here.
你为什么不想让我们知道你的真实身份
Why don't you want us to know who you really are?
正在对比指纹
需要5分钟
难道你不想逃避过去 做个全新的人吗
Haven't you wanted to escape your past? To be someone else?
重新来过吗
Start again?
打 印 中...
请   稍   后
- 好了 我们搞定了 - 嘿
- Okay. We're clear. - Hey.
你怎么知道监视器上看不出来呢
How do you know it looks good on the monitors?
你那熊样 让我对你提不起欲望了
It is so hard for me to love you when you do that.
你真是蠢死了
You're so stupid.
可能藏身处
等等 等下 别动 有个新玩意
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. There's something new here.
- 看见没 - 没 看不到
- Do you see it? - No, I don't see it.
在天花板上 就在那儿
It's up on the ceiling. Right there.
- 让我看看 - 等等
- Let me see. - Hold on.
不等 让我看吧 让我看看
No, let me see. Let me see.
看见没
See?
退后
Back up.
- 退后 退后 退后 - 那是什么
- Back up, back up, back up. - What is it?
那是个传感器
That's a sensor.
- 你怎么知道 - 我就是知道
- How do you know? - I know. I just know.
现在真要拿这个说事吗
Do you really wanna talk about this right now?
那得看我们现在到底在谈什么 不是吗
That depends on what we're talking about, doesn't it?
好吧 乔伊
Okay, Joey.
我高中的时候呢 有时会私闯民宅
In high school, I used to break into houses sometimes.
- 你闯...  - 闯进一些高档住宅
- You broke... - Really expensive houses.
所以我才知道那是什么玩意
That's how I know what that is.
好 好 这么说你原来是个贼
Great. Great, so you were a thief?
不 不 不是 只是进去看看电视 试试衣服 懂吗
No, no, no! I used to watch TV and try on clothes, you know?
除非衣服太合适了 我才拿走 就那么多
Unless the clothes fit. And that's all.
还有没有别的事瞒着我
Is there anything else you want to tell me about?
有犯过什么重罪没告诉我的吗
You got any felonies you failed to mention?
什么 这个问题先放一放 行吧
Excuse me? Take it down a notch. All right?
因为你可能会把那玩意激活了
Because you probably would've set that shit off.
好吧 帮个忙 想些积极的事
All right. Do me a favor. Visualize something positive.
如果可以去世界上任何一个地方 你会做些什么
If you could be anywhere in the world, what would you be doing?
尼克 有些事咱们没预料到
Nick, we got something that isn't on the plans.
尼克 说话啊
Nick? Come in.
说啊 说啥都行
Come on, anything.
尼克 我需要帮忙 哥们 我们在这儿遇到麻烦了
Nick, I need you, man. We've got a problem here.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们不知道这是什么东西 应该是种传感器
We don't know what it is. It's some kind of sensor.
比如说 如果是我选的话 我想去罗博图酒店吃饭
Like, if it was me, I'd be having dinner at Roberto's.
跟我说说吧
Tell me about it.
亲爱的 告诉他你看到了什么
Babe, tell him what you're looking at.
天花板上有一个小型的黑色的传感器 大约4英寸
It's a little black bulb on the ceiling about 4 inches across.
最好是布朗克斯鸡尾酒里掺点意大利料
It's this little Italian joint in the Bronx.
罗博图饭店的块菌做得最好吃了
Roberto does amazing things with truffles.
- 来上一瓶酒... - 听着真诱人
- Bottle of wine... - That sounds hot.
兄弟 那点信息不够 你说什么 快回答我
I'm gonna need a little more than that, bro. What are you saying? I need an answer here.
听着 咱们遇到的这事儿
Listen. This thing that we got here.
我觉得我们该冷静点
I think we should cool it down
免得你惹麻烦
before you get into trouble.
听着 尼克亲 笨蛋 这不是烛光晚餐
Look, Nicky. Numbnuts. This is not a candlelit dinner.
我们都急出汗了 到底是什么东西
We're sweating down here. What is it?
这东西
This thing?
我正在想呢
I'm just looking out for you.
她身材很火吗
Is she hot?
- 噢 - 这是个热传感器
- Oh! - It's a heat sensor.
我们得让它冷却下来
We have to cool it down.
- 冷却 - 对
- Cool it down. - Yeah.
- 冷却下来 - 是啊
- Cool it down. - Yes.
你从窗户爬进来 请我去吃饭 如何
Why don't you come in this window and I'll let you take me to lunch?
挺诱人啊
It's tempting.
不过我觉得不是个好主意
But I don't think it's a good idea.
难道你还有更好的去处
You got someplace better to be?
如果我没说错的话
If I'm right,
你从我烟头上提取的指纹的检测结果 就快出来了吧
that print you pulled off our cigarette's about to come through.
指纹检测结果能让我查到什么
What's it gonna tell me?
搞定
Bags.
乔·沃克
麦克·阿克曼
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
- 所有人注意 - 说
- Listen up. - Go.
默瑟 查到跳楼人的身份了 他是个逃犯
Mercer, I got an ID on your jumper. He's an escaped convict.
叫尼克·卡西迪
Nick Cassidy.
卡西迪 那个从大卫·英格兰德手上偷走钻石的警察
Cassidy. The cop that stole the diamond off David Englander?
价值四千万美元的钻石
The $40 million diamond.
我就知道我认出这个人了
I knew I recognized this mutt.
这家酒店是大卫·英格兰德的
Englander owns this hotel.
他的办公室就在这儿 他的珠宝交易中心就在街对面
His office is here. His Jewelry Exchange is right across the street.
- 到底发生什么事了 - 他的小纸条上说什么了
- What the hell is going on? - What did his little note say?
- "当我进入 我将步出..." - "无辜"
- "I will exit as I entered..." - "Innocent".
- 他想让人们觉得不是他没有偷钻石 - 做白日梦吧
- He wants people to think he didn't do it. - Good luck with that.
我觉得他最更想让人看他表演吧
I think he's more interested in just having an audience.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
把他档案调出来 找到他的家人 翻翻他的牢房
Pull his file. Find his family. Toss his cell.
他的搭档是谁
Who'd he ride with?
麦克·阿克曼
Mike Ackerman.
天哪
Jesus.
简直不敢相信
I can't believe this.
他怎么样了
How's he doing?
他现在玩得很爽 把我们耍得团团转
Well, he's playing this very cool. Like this is all some sort of game.
他一直坚持说自己是无辜的
He always insisted he was innocent.
你相信他吗
Do you believe that?
听着 我和他做了5年搭档
Look, he was my partner for five years.
那你觉得他会跳吗
So do you think he would jump?
他已经一无所有了
He's got nothing to lose.
我马上就来
I'm on my way.
保安部 我是内斯特
First Line Security. This is Nestor.
你好 内斯特 我是马库斯警官 我在罗斯福酒店里
Yeah, Nestor. This is Detective Marcus over at the Roosevelt Hotel.
听我指挥 我要你去对面检查一下保险室
You work for me today. I need you to open up Englander's shop.
- 警官... - 立刻去
- Detective... - Right now.
就是这了 宝贝 给我凿子
That's it, baby. Chisel.
大家好
Hello, everybody.
很高兴大家都能来
I'm glad you could make it.
我多希望我父亲能看到这一天
I wish my dad could see this.
他是个移民
He was an immigrant.
兢兢业业做着珠宝贸易
Worked his ass off in the jewelry trade.
当我决定把所有的资本都投在房地产时 他担心得要死
So he was more than a little anxious when I decided to risk it all in real estate.
这就是我买下"帝王之钻"的意义 这表明我有能力做到
That's why I bought the Monarch Diamond. You know, when I could.
用来纪念他
To honor him.
你们都知道 3年前经济危机的时候
You know, three years ago, when the market tanked,
他们都说我们完蛋了
they said we were finished.
- 记得吗 - 记得
- Remember? - Yeah.
但那正是这个国家最伟大之处
But that's what's great about this country.
如果你努力争取 你总能力挽狂澜 对吧
If you want it bad enough, you can make it back. Hmm?
对
True.
在这个城市里 在这个岛屿上
In this city, on this island,
我们不是去上班
we don't go to work,
- 而是去上战场 - 对
- we go to war. - Yes!
如果有人从你那夺走了什么
And if somebody takes something from you,
- 你就再抢回来 - 抢回来 抢回来
- you take it back. - Hear, hear!
连本带利
And more.
几年前有人偷了我一件珍贵的珠宝
I had one precious jewel taken from me a few years ago.
但现在我又有新的珠宝 而这件谁都偷不走
But now I've got another that no one will ever steal from me.
女士们先生们 我们终于聚在这里
Ladies and gentlemen, we're finally here.
为了我的新珠宝 "王者之冠"干杯
To my new jewel, the Monarch Spire!
- 干杯 - 祝贺你 大卫
- Cheers! - Congratulations, David.
圆满成功呀
You pulled it off.
打扰下 长官 他们已经查到跳楼者的身份了
Excuse me, sir. They've ID'd the jumper.
- 那又怎么样 - 是尼克·卡西迪
- So what? - It's Nick Cassidy.
尼克·卡西迪
Nick Cassidy.
重罪犯
Convicted felon.
我没打算让你失望 莉迪亚
I didn't mean to disappoint you, Lydia.
只是好奇 这个小把戏有什么意义吗
I'm just curious, does this little show have a point?
因为我开始严重怀疑你的自杀意图了
'Cause I'm seriously starting to doubt your suicidal tendencies.
是的 我确定你上司也正准备 派人立刻到街对面去
And I'm sure that your boss is gonna be sending a team across the street right now.
等等 尼克 我们还没准备好呢
Hold on! Nick, we're not ready yet!
是的 立刻会去
Yeah, right now.
开我玩笑很好玩吗
Are you having fun jerking me around?
你是要控制我吗
Are you trying to manipulate me?
不是
No!
2年前 我给人做兼职爵士乐师 很简单
Two years ago, I'm doing a moonlighting gig. Real simple.
护送大卫·英格兰德连同 "帝王之钻" 到查帕夸镇
Escort David Englander up to Chappaqua with the Monarch Diamond.
昨天我以偷窃钻石的罪名被判处25年监禁
Yesterday, I'm doing 25 years for apparently stealing it.
今天呢 今天我要殊死一搏 不过需要你的帮助
And today? Today I'm putting it all on the damn line. And I need your help.
你疯了
You are nuts.
你不会袖手旁观的 记得吗
You care, remember?
你打错算盘了 尼克
You played this all wrong, Nick.
大卫·英格兰德陷害了我
David Englander set me up.
你本来可以在墨西哥某个海滩喝杯酒逍遥快活
You could've been sipping tequila on a beach in Mexico.
是啊 说的好听
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
瞻前顾后 提心吊胆
Looking over your shoulder, sleeping with one eye open.
那不叫自由
That isn't freedom.
站在这里对着一堆镜头就叫自由
Standing here in front of all these TV cameras is?
至少在众目睽睽之下没人敢对我下黑手
No one is gonna shoot me with their grandmother watching.
干脆你告诉我你还有什么预谋吧
Maybe you should tell me the rest of your plan.
我想要证明我是无辜的
The plan is to prove that I'm innocent.
这算什么 这就是我的重审法庭
And this? This is my retrial.
我没有犯罪
I'm innocent!
我是无辜的
I'm an innocent man!
你听见没有 莉迪亚 我是无辜的
Did you get that, Lydia? I'm innocent!
你回去告诉你上司 我绝不会走回头路
Now you go downstairs and tell your bosses that I'm not going back.
你能帮帮我吗 告诉我 莉迪亚
Can you do that for me? Tell me, Lydia.
好吧 尼克
Yeah, Nick.
我去去就来
I'll go do that.
来人了 四人组
Here they come. Party of four.
让他们过去 让开
Let 'em through. Make way.
- 小心背后 - 退后 退后
- Watch your backs. - Stay back! Stay back!
尼克 听见了吗 拖住他们
Hey, Nick, you hearing me? We need more time.
好
Okay.
快点 这边
Come on. Come on.
来点欢呼声吧
Let's make it rain.
你不能从这儿过
You can't cross here.
那是什么
What is that?
是钱
It's money!
我爱这家伙
I love this guy!
让开 让开
Make way! Make way!
- 入口在那儿 - 明白 明白
- That's the entrance. - Got it. Yeah. Got it.
给 拿着摄像机
Here. Take the camera.
这边 就这儿
Right here. Right here.
快让开 快让开
Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
他们成了禽兽
They're animals!
- 我来 坚持不了多久 - 你去拿工具 去拿工具
- I can't get it. It won't stay! - Get the gear! Get the gear.
- 快让路 让路 - 快走
- Keep out of the way! Out of the way! - Move!
一边去
Get out of here!
咋回事儿 宝贝
How are you doing, babe?
粘不上去
It won't stick!
慢慢来 你可以的
Just take a breath! You can do it.
你们回避一下
I need you guys to turn around.
好了 可以了
All right. We're good.
乔伊 他们进去了
Joey, they're in.
快 快 快 我们该走了
Go! Go! Go! We gotta go!
乔伊 说话
Joey, talk to me.
快 快 快
Go! Go! Go!
解除15楼警报
Disarm 15, lobby.
快点
Come on.
还有大厅传感器
Hallway sensors.
这狗日的在我大楼里干什么
What is the son of a bitch doing on my building?
不清楚 英格兰德先生
I don't know, Mr. Englander,
但是我可以向您保证 一切都在我们的掌控之下
but I can assure you the situation's completely under control.
- 掌控之下 - 是的
- Under control? - Yeah.
- 你去外面看了吗 - 去了
- Have you been outside? - Yeah.
这事发生在今天 就不是什么偶然事件
It's no accident that this is happening today.
两小时之后我有一个很重要的新闻发布会
I've got a major press conference in two hours.
卡西迪除了进监狱可算是上天无路下地无门
The only place that Cassidy's going is back into custody or splat on 45th.
你他娘的真是让我蛋疼
This is a goddamned embarrassment.
你马上解决这事儿 要不然的话
You wrap this up now, or tomorrow you're sucking fumes
你就准备老死在无人海岛吧 你明白不
on a parking scooter in Staten Island. You got it?
明白
Yeah.
妮娜 帮我联系市长办公室
Nina! Get me the Mayor's office.
这就是英格兰德放奢侈品的保险柜
This is where Englander entertains the high-rollers.
1-9-6-7 确认
1-9-6-7, pound.
解除金库警报
Disarm the vault room.
地板连接着地震感应器
The floors are wired with seismic sensors.
那边还有光电感应器和体热感应器
And over there we've got light sensors and body-heat sensors.
- 哇 - 你还没进来就玩完了
- Whoa! - And that's before you even get to the vault.
一切正常
It's all clear.
谁能潜入这么牛叉的地方
Nobody's getting into that beast.
您先请 先生们
After you, gentlemen.
什么事
Yeah?
我是内斯特 英格兰德金库一切正常
It's Nestor. Englander's is clear, Detective.
好的 至少那狗娘养的不会咬着我的屁股不放了
Good. I don't need that son of a bitch crawling up my ass any more.
收到
Roger that.
咱们走
Let's go.
默瑟
Mercer.
这帮人来干什么
Why is tactical here?
- 这可是越狱事件 对吧 - 忙你自己的事情吧
- It is a fugitive situation, isn't it? - Do your thing.
现在什么情况
So where are we at?
从他的表现看来他坚信自己是无辜的
He is acting like he really believes that he's innocent.
是吗 那是什么意思
Yeah? What's that make him?
他要么是个实在人 要么就是个反社会者
An honest man or a sociopath.
这种人不可信 这场表演可以谢幕了
He ain't an honest man. And I'm gonna put an end to this show out here.
- 你能把他带回来吗 - 没问题
- Can you get him off the ledge? - Yes.
他对我有好感
He likes me.
马库斯 给她点时间吧
Marcus, give her a little more time.
给你15分钟 之后我就叫反恐特警了 明白
You have 15 minutes, then I'm sending tactical. You got it?
伙计们
Lutz?
来吧 大盗小姐
Let's go, thief!
你确定没有什么要说的了吗
You sure there's nothing else you wanna tell me?
快闪开 走开 闪开
Come on. Move! Come on!
我去
Shit!
闪开
Come on!
- 没什么要说的 - 你在惹我生气
- Nothing you wanna tell me? - You're starting to chafe me.
你不会想知道所有事情的 没有人会这样
You don't wanna know everything. Nobody does.
我就想
Sure I do.
关于男朋友
Boyfriends?
还是女朋友
Girlfriends?
还是最棒的性爱体验
Best sex of my life?
那个... 很明显啊
Well... Obviously.
好吧 喂 等等
Okay, wait. Hold on a sec.
"帝王之钻" 最近为大卫·英格兰德所持有
The Monarch Diamond was most recently held by David Englander
直到被尼克·卡西迪偷走 也就是这个跳楼的人
until it was stolen by Nick Cassidy, the man on the ledge,
他把钻石分割成无法追踪痕迹的小块 然后卖掉
who was said to have cut it up into untraceable pieces and sold it.
- 跟马戏团表演一样 - 打死我都不信啊
- It's a circus. - I don't believe this.
噢 天哪
Oh, man.
没时间了 尼克
Time is running out here, Nick.
反恐特警来了 别再玩我了
Tactical's on the scene and I am tired of being played.
对于拿走你一切的人 你会怎么做 嗯
How far would you go to take down a man that stole everything from you? Huh?
夺走了你的尊严
Your honor.
你的家庭 你会怎么做 你会不惜一切代价
Your family. What would you do? You'd do whatever it takes.
我护送他到教堂公司后 他的两个蒙着脸的走狗
After I drove him to Chappaqua, two of his thugs, guys in masks,
把我撂倒在地 而他就站在那儿笑
knocked me out while he just stood there and smiled.
- 但是法官不信你那一套 尼克 - 没错
- The jury didn't believe that, Nick. - That's right.
我自己的律师都不信
And neither did my lawyer.
两年来 我一直拿自己的头撞墙
And I have spent two years banging my head against a brick wall,
因为我知道 那块 "帝王之钻"一直就没有丢
'cause I know that the Monarch never left his hand.
英格兰德干嘛要贼喊捉贼
Why would Englander steal his own diamond?
他赔了雷曼3000万 在房地产大跌中又赔了2000万
He lost $30 million to Lehman. He lost another 20 in the real-estate bust.
他那会儿离破产不远了
He was that close to being bankrupt.
- 如果他需要钱他大可以卖了钻石
- If he needed cash, he could've just sold it. - No.
他不会那么干 因为他不想被同行耻笑 他自尊心太强了
He wouldn't do that, 'cause he wouldn't want to be humiliated. He's too damn proud.
在我被审判两周后
Two weeks after my conviction,
伦敦的路易斯给了他一张4000万的赔偿支票
Lloyd's of London sent him a check for 40 million for a claim.
于是 噗 他东山再起了
And, poof! He's back.
求你了 你一定要相信我
Come on. I need you to believe me.
- 求你了  - 那群走狗是谁
- Come on! - Who were the thugs?
我不知道 不过我知道英格兰德只利用警察
I don't know. But I know that Englander only uses cops.
警察
Cops?
你能体会那种所有人都背叛你的感觉吗
You know what it's like to have everyone turn their back on you.
连最亲的人都不例外
Even those closest to you.
今天才是你真正做一回救世主的时候了
Today is the day that you can really save someone.
求你了
Please.
你要是骗我 哪怕是只字片语 我第一个就把你推下去
If you are lying to me about any of this, I'm gonna push you off myself.
看好他
Watch him.
你使唤我们是越来越顺手了
You're getting a little too comfortable barking orders.
纽约警察局
什么情况
What's up?
纽约警察局
他怎样了
How's he doing?
纽约警察局
默瑟还没动手呢
Mercer hasn't killed him yet.
他说话了吗
Is he talking?
你知道吗 麦克
You know what, Mikey?
总有一天你会走错地方 被人弄死
One day you're gonna stick your dick in the wrong door and someone's gonna slam it.
我找到了一些他服刑监狱的文件
I've got some papers from his cell in Sing Sing.
拿上去给多尔蒂
Take 'em up to Dougherty.
我看看
Let me see those.
- 我拿上去吧 - 好吧
- I'll take these up. - You do that.
安吉 安吉 安吉
Angie, Angie, Angie.
咋啦
What?
你真是秀色可餐 妞
You're moving artwork, girl.
话说回来 你最棒的一次是跟谁
So what was the best sex of your life?
- 这还用说 当然是你 - 是吗
- You, Joey. - Yeah?
不过 高中时候有个家伙
Well, there was this one guy in high school.
比我大 他的手...
He was older. He had these hands...
别跟我开这种玩笑 听到没 走吧
Don't even mess with me. Yeah? Let's go.
那是什么时候的事
When was that?
- 案发一周后 - 人赃俱获了吗
- A week after the heist. - Did I have anything?
谁都想着会起诉定罪 但案子却不了了之
Everyone expected indictments, but the case fell apart.
- 很好 - 我就知道这么多
- That's great. - That's all I got.
好的 多谢啦
Yeah. Thanks a lot.
你确定街对面没发生什么事吗
Are we sure nothing's happening across the street?
他不可能一个东西偷两回
You can't steal something twice.
更别说钻石已经被切割成那么多块了
Especially if it's been cut into a million pieces.
如果他没偷呢
What if he didn't do it?
拜托 默瑟
Please, Mercer.
- 马库斯 - 请讲
- Marcus? - Go.
会不会还有别的警察掺和那个英格兰德的案子
What if there were other cops involved in this Englander thing?
你要是想在局里受更多人唾弃
If you're trying to get yourself even more despised within the department,
那你算是找对地方了
I'd say you're really on to something.
我刚查到卡西迪和信息调查局有合作
I just found out Cassidy was cooperating with IA.
关于什么
About what?
你记不记得有个人带着价值100万的可卡因
You remember when somebody disappeared about a million bucks' worth of cocaine
凭空消失了吗
out of evidence?
卡西迪说那人叫乔·沃克 记录在案的也是同一人
Cassidy gave 'em a name, Joe Walker. Same name he checked in under.
卡西迪被抓一周后 在哈德逊发现了沃克和他的车子
And a week after Cassidy went up, Walker and his car got pulled out of the Hudson.
没错 酒精指数是.23
Yeah. He had a blood alcohol level of .23.
你在后边追的时候 为什么不停下来
Why don't you stop while you're behind?
跟沃克一起工作的人最有陷害卡西迪的嫌疑
Whoever was in it with Walker had every reason to set Cassidy up.
你不知道沃克干了什么 这么说太武断了
You don't know that Walker did it. It's just an allegation.
我知道卡西迪站在窗台上不是为了自杀
I know Cassidy's not on this ledge to say goodbye.
是吗 他说什么了
Yeah? What's he saying?
"去你的"
"Fuck you."
- 伙计们 叫你的人各就各位 马上 - 收到
- Lutz. Get your people into position. Now! - Roger that.
好啦 游戏开始 先生们
Okay. It's game time, gentlemen.
- 出发 把夹子口上 - 好
- Let's go. Let's get your straps on. - Yes.
- 把袋子和耳机给我 - 明白
- Pouch and headset, please. - Got it.
袋子 耳机
Pouch. Headset.
耳机
Headset.
出发 走 走 走
Let's go, go, go.
小菜一碟 对吧
Piece of cake, right?
- 不行 - 不行 你说不行 什么意思
- No. - No? What do you mean, no?
- 我觉得自己进不去 - 宝贝 听着
- I don't think I'll fit in there. - Babe, listen.
我的重量你承受不住 明白吗
You can't hold my weight. All right?
没时间讨论这个问题了
We don't have time to talk about this.
照以前训练好的做就行 不然尼克会杀了我
Just like we practiced or Nick'll kill me.
尼克会杀了你 我现在就杀了你
Nick will kill you? I'm gonna kill you.
发怒吧 在排气管中发怒吧
Be mad. Just be mad in the vent.
给我出去
Get out of here.
没听见吗
Did I stutter?
看见那个东西没 看见没
You see that? You see that?
把人压迫太紧了 就会出现这种结果
This is what happens when a man gets pushed too far!
懂吗 总是要屁民来承受这些痛苦
Right? It's always the little guy who takes the hit!
监狱里都是穷人
There's no rich guys in prison.
我们总有一天会变成和尼克·卡西迪一样的人
Nick Cassidy could be any of us!
突发新闻
现场直播
钻石大盗让整个城市处于紧张状态
尼克·卡西迪一直强调他是无辜的
Nick Cassidy has always maintained his innocence.
你真的相信他偷了 "帝王之钻"吗
Do you believe he actually stole the Monarch Diamond?
我希望他偷了 是我我也偷 谁不想偷啊
I hope he did. I would've done it. Who wouldn't have?
- 麦克·阿克曼 - 杰克·多尔蒂 欢迎参加宴会
- Mike Ackerman. - Jack Dougherty. Welcome to the party.
- 这是从新新监狱带来的资料 - 很好
- I brought the papers from Sing Sing. - Great.
嗨 我是莉迪亚·默瑟
Hi. Lydia Mercer.
- 我要和他说话 - 噢...
- I wanna talk to him. - Yeah.
你在帮英格兰德做事吗 还是只有尼克而已
You ever moonlight for Englander, or was it just Nick?
我不知道你在说些什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
是乔·沃克帮你们设计了这一切吗
Was it a Joe Walker who set that detail up for you guys?
- 是又怎样 - 所以真是他做的
- So what? - So he did?
我没说是他做的 我只是说 "是又怎样?"
I didn't say he did. I said, "So what?"
你就甭费心思靠近他了
You're not getting near him.
那是我的朋友
That's my friend out there.
这里我说了算
And this is my scene.
多尔蒂 你能跟她说一下吗
Dougherty? Will you talk to her?
听着 伙计 我们都得听她的
Look, man. It's the lady's call.
如果需要你的话 我们会叫你的
We will call you if we need you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我希望你知道自已到底在做些什么
You better know what the hell you're doing.
这是什么
And what's this?
我带了些吃的来 我想这孩子可能饿了
I brought up some food. I thought the kid might be hungry.
你怎么样了 孩子
How are you doing, kid?
我还在坚持着
I'm hanging in there.
祝你胃口好
Bon appetit.
你在里边待得咋样 宝贝
How are you doing in there, babe?
我做不到
I can't do it.
什么 宝贝 时间不等人啊 我们现在该走了 快点
What? Babe, the clock's ticking. We gotta go now. Come on.
别害怕 安吉 今天天气不错 人们在欢呼呢
Don't panic, Angie. It's a sunny day. The crowd's cheering.
耶
Yeah!
听听 他们都在为你欢呼
Listen to this. They're all cheering for you.
他们都站在我们这边 安吉
They're all on our side, Angie.
耶
Yeah!
我进来了
I'm in.
好的
Good.
放松点
Just relax.
集中精神
Keep it together.
你动作要快 以免热传感器捕捉到你
Let's do this thing fast, before the heat sensor catches up with you.
啊
Ah!
轻如羽毛啊
Light as a feather.
我听到了
I heard that!
好的 好的
Yeah, yeah.
特警队已经就位 你快进来吧
Tactical is setting up. You need to come in.
现在还不行
I can't yet.
现在全世界都知道你是谁了 尼克
The whole world knows who you are now, Nick.
你让每个记者都开始调查你的过去
You've inspired every reporter to look into your story.
如果你是清白的 事情会真相大白的
If you're innocent, it'll come out.
我不会再回拘留所了 他们就会杀了我
And if I go back into custody, they're gonna kill me.
尼克 别扔下我一个人在这里
Nick! Don't leave me hanging here.
听着 我只需要你再帮我争取一些时间 相信我
Look. I just need you to buy me some time. Trust me.
我那时也相信那个警察
I trusted that cop.
桥上的那个
On the bridge.
我以为已经把他劝服了
I thought I had him wired.
我本来可以离开了
I was supposed to be relieved,
但我留下了 因为我知道
but I stayed on, because I knew.
但那时
Only then,
我突然间不确定了
suddenly I didn't know.
你的直觉没有错
There's nothing wrong with your instincts.
再给我点时间
Give me more time.
嘿 默瑟
Hey, Mercer.
你来看看这个
You're gonna wanna take a look at this.
他的牢房里有炸弹动力学的书
He had bomb schematics in his cell.
安吉 是我
Angie, it's me.
好了 你看到什么了
Okay, what do you see?
我看到一堆电线
I see a mass of wires
从一块电路板上延伸出来
coming out of a circuit board.
好的 现在先找到主处理器
Okay, now find the main processor.
它跟大号的低层房子很像
It'll look like a big low building.
- 找到了吗 - 找到了
- You got it? - Got it.
- 找到了 - 好的
- I got it. - Okay.
就像练习过的那样 把它弄短路 切断传感器
Like you practiced, we're gonna short it out to take out the sensors.
先把红线剪断
First, cut the red wire.
红线
Red wire?
这里全是红线
They're all red wire.
尼克 是灯光的原因 宝贝 拣最红的那根
Nick, it's her light. Babe, pick the reddest one.
- 等等 - 她可以的 尼克
- Hold on. - She can do it, Nick.
闭嘴 先听我说
Shut up. Just listen to me.
如果你选错了线 我们就要倒大霉了
If you out the wrong one, all hell is gonna break loose.
没事 宝贝 剪吧 宝贝
Come on, babe. Come on, baby.
好了
Done.
哇唔
Whoo!
好样的
Good girl.
好了 现在把那根线接到处理器上
Okay, now touch the wire to the processor.
好的 这个简单多了
Okay, that sounds easy enough.
- 可能会有些火花 - 啊
- It might spark a bit. - Ah!
安吉
Angie!
安吉啊
Angie?
安吉
听得到我说话吗
Do you hear me?
- 你还好吗 - 现在别跟我说话 好吗
- Are you all right? - Don't talk to me right now, okay?
我现在可以确定防爆小组已经赶到现场
I can now confirm that the bomb squad has just arrived on the scene
神秘的跳楼者
特警队也正在朝罗斯福酒店的屋檐上爬
and tactical units are on their way up to the roof of the Roosevelt Hotel.
神秘的跳楼者
这个逃犯的时间不多了
Time is running out for this escaped criminal.
你藏了炸弹吗
Is there a bomb?
你要我相信你 却给我来这一套
You asked for my trust, and then this.
现在是你做出选择的时候了 记得吗
Well, this is the moment you make your choice. Remember?
默瑟 特警队要出动了 离开窗户那儿
Mercer, tactical's a go. It's time to clear the window.
全看你的决定了
It's your call.
撤吧 默瑟
Stand down, Mercer.
你们开枪之前他就会说出来
He will go over before he gets taken down.
把我们过去的成绩记录和你的对照一下
That's assuming our track record's on par with yours.
好了
All right.
炸弹协议书上说 除了谈判专家 我们可以疏散任何人 清空大楼
The bomb protocol says we clear everybody but the negotiator. Clear the building.
没发现炸弹 这只是他的缓兵之计 他在耍你
No one has found a bomb. This threat is a stall! He's playing you!
他选择你 是因为你的状态根本无法应付
He picked you, 'cause you're in no condition to do your job!
这是我的地盘 我的谈判
This is my scene! My negotiation!
该死的 多尔蒂 把她从那儿拉出来 马上
God damn it! Dougherty, pull her out of there! Now!
莉迪亚 快点 离开窗户那儿
Lydia, come on! Clear the window!
你在做什么
What are you doing?
嘿
Hey!
嗨
Hi!
上帝啊
Jesus Christ!
全体人员 停止行动 重复一遍 不要动
All units! This is a hold! Repeat, no go!
- 默瑟 快回来 - 闭嘴
- Mercer, get back in here! - Shut up!
退后 闭上嘴
Stay back! Just shut up!
好了
Set.
见证奇迹的时刻
Moment of truth.
看看里面有什么
Let's see what we've got.
- 我现在爱死你了 - 噢 是吗
- I am so hot for you right now. - Oh, yeah?
是的
Yeah.
看看 我们来这里只有一个目的 一个目的
Uh-uh-uh-uh. We're only here for one thing. One thing.
- 好 我要过来了 - 快点
- Okay, I'm coming over. - Come on.
该死
Holy shit.
慢慢来 别急
Nice and slow. Nice and easy.
该死
Holy shit!
- 要找个人把她也抓住吗 - 你开玩笑吧
- You want us to try and grab her, too?  - Are you kidding me?
我们搞砸了 全是我们的错
We screw up this, it's all our asses.
看看这些 看看这些
Check in these, check in these.
这么说 你相信我是清白的了
Does this mean you believe I'm innocent?
有这个可能 告诉我你没藏炸弹
It's a possibility. Tell me there's no bomb.
你看到钻石了吗
Do you see the diamond here?
- 应该在这里啊 对吧 - 我知道应该在这里
- It's gotta be here! Right? - I know it's gotta be here.
噢 不是吧
Oh, no.
- 妈的 没有 - 没有
- Hell, no. - No?
嘿 尼克
Hey, Nick.
只是...
Just...
- 只是... - 怎么了
- Just... - What?
乔伊 告诉我 告诉我你找到什么了
Joey, talk to me. Tell me what you got.
你在和谁说话
Who are you talking to?
谁是乔伊
Who's Joey?
我在偷钻石
I'm stealing the diamond.
这是第一次
For the first time.
钻石不在这里
It's not here.
- 你说什么 - 对不起 哥们
- Say again? - I'm sorry, bro.
钻石不在这里
It's not here.
钻石不在保险柜里
It's not in the vault.
噢 妈的
Oh, shit.
好 乔伊 你知道该怎么做
Okay, Joey. You know what to do.
嗯 知道了
Yeah. Copy that.
我们要在5分钟之内离开 准备开新闻发布会 先生
We need to leave in five minutes for the press conference, sir.
好
Good.
英格兰德大楼警报器响了
We've got an alarm at Englander's.
封锁大楼 别让任何人出去
Seal the building. No one gets out.
所有小组请注意 街对面的警报器响了
All squads be advised. We've got an alarm across the street.
上帝啊
Jesus Christ!
开什么玩笑
You're kidding me.
爬上去 去看看
Get up there. Take a look.
他们在楼里的某个地方 从第15层楼的天花板开始找
They're somewhere in the building. Start with the ceiling on 15.
别让他们进来
Keep them out of here.
伙计们 等一会儿
Guys, give us a second.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
- 把他们找出来 - 正在找
- Find them! - I'm on it.
听着 如果我能找到沃克的档案呢
Okay, listen. What if I could get Walker's IA file?
没关系 里面什么都没有
It's not gonna matter. There's nothing in it.
不 那些家伙非常谨慎
No, those guys, they're cautious and paranoid.
他们十分多疑 他们不查出点什么是不会罢休的
They don't put shit in the file unless they can prove it six ways to Sunday.
但那不代表他们不知道
But that doesn't mean that they don't know.
好了 马库斯 她要回来了
All right, Marcus, she's coming back in now.
- 让你的人就位 - 所有小组待命
- Get your people set. - All squads stand by.
上帝啊 默瑟 你可是要面对荷枪实弹啊
Jesus, Mercer. You got a giant set of balls.
你再不回来 他们就要行动了
They're gonna hang you by 'em, but they are huge.
我们刚才跟内务部说到哪里了
Where are we with Internal Affairs?
好吧 他在等你电话
Okay. He's expecting your call.
这里是内务部 我是埃文斯
Internal Affairs. Evans.
我是丽迪雅·默瑟探员 多尔蒂说你有事要跟我讲
This is Detective Lydia Mercer. Dougherty said that you would talk to me.
嗯 没错
Yeah, that's right.
你应该看看这个
You should see this.
这是什么
What is it?
给我五分钟就好
Just give me five minutes.
阿克曼 把门打开
Ackerman, open this door!
警官 我命令你 马上给我回来 把门打开
Detective, I'm telling you right now! Get back here and open this door!
嘿 搭档
Hey, partner.
你准备跳了 还是怎么着
So are you gonna jump or what?
他妈的把门打开 阿克曼
Open the fucking door, Ackerman!
他们人呢 那个谈判员呢
Where is everyone? Where's the negotiator?
别管他们了 卡斯 这是你我之间的事 懂吗
Don't worry about them. It's just me and you on this, Cass, okay?
多尔蒂 那边到底发生什么事了
Dougherty, what the hell's going on there?
阿克曼闯进来 把我们锁在外面了
Ackerman breached the door! He locked us out!
- 什么 - 混蛋
- What? - Son of a bitch!
好吧 待会打给我 待会打给我
All right. Call me back. Call me back.
离开窗台 进来如何
Why don't you come on in off this ledge?
我来帮你
Let me help you.
- 不行 - 别发疯了 卡斯 快点
- I can't do that. - Don't be crazy, Cass. Come in here.
卡斯
Cass!
嘿 我来帮你
Let me help you.
我一直就怀疑你跟这事有关
I always wondered if you were involved in this.
- 跟什么事有关 - 现在有人在和信息调查局的人谈话
- Involved in what? - There is someone talking to IA right now.
他们会查出哪些人呢
Whose name are they gonna come up with?
嘿 我是你的朋友 拉住我的手
I'm your friend. Take my hand.
用枪把锁打开
Shoot the lock!
好 大家后退 离远点
All right, guys, clear out.
谁的名字
Whose name?
你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
- 我是你的朋友 - 天哪
- I'm your friend. - Jesus Christ.
- 离我远点 - 快 快 快
- Get away from me! - Go! Go! Go!
抓住他们
Take 'em.
我是你的朋友
I'm your friend!
那你为什么看上去充满罪恶感
Then why do you look so guilty?
不是吧
No!
噢 不是吧
Oh, no!
妈的
Shit!
嫌疑犯回到大楼了 看紧走廊
Suspect is back in the building. Secure the corridor.
告诉马库斯 撤走特警队 马上撤退
Get Marcus to call off tactical! Now!
默瑟 回来 已经不关我们的事了
Mercer! Get back here! This isn't our show any more!
阿提卡 他们要动手了
Attica! They're gonna take him down!
阿提卡 阿提卡
Attica! Attica!
- 嘿 嘿 嘿 保罗 照那个人 - 快点 他们抓不住咱们
- Hey, hey, hey! Paul, get this guy! - Come on. They can't stop us!
- 让开 - 跟我来 跟我来
- Get out of my way! - Come with me. Come with me.
- 来人啊 救命啊 - 好 先生 嘿 嘿 嘿
- Come on, somebody! - Okay. Sir! Hey, hey, hey!
你想干嘛 把我们所有人都抓走吗
What are they gonna do, arrest us all?
- 先生 先生 - 你想开枪 就开枪打他啊
- Sir! Sir! - You wanna shoot something, shoot that!
封锁21楼到24楼 派人搜查第20层 带上入住名单
Lock down floors 21 to 24. Assemble personnel on 20, with a guest list.
- 我们逐层往上查 每个房间都不放过 - 大伙听着 两人一组
- We will sweep up, room to room. - Everyone break in teams of two.
地毯式搜索 翻个底朝天
Floor by floor, rolling cover.
对不起
Sorry!
操...
What the...
看看这东西
LOOK at this.
- 什么东西 - 加热包
- What? - Heat packs.
肯定是这东西触发了感应器
That's what tripped the sensor.
他们为什么要故意触发警报器呢
Why would they deliberately set the alarm off?
这枪不错啊
This is a nice gun.
我蛮喜欢 看上去很贵的样子
I like it. Looks expensive.
- 你是谁 - 不记得我了
- Who are you? - You don't remember me?
我是他弟弟
I'm the brother.
每天法庭上坐在尼克后面 坐了五个礼拜
The one sitting behind Nick in court every day for five weeks.
现在想起来了吗
Remember me now?
有点印象了
How quaint.
还有你那可人的小吉娃娃
And your adorable little Chihuahua.
- 她是个活人 - 闭嘴
- She speaks, too. - Shut your mouth!
转过去 手放桌子上
Turn around, put your hands on the table.
多谢帮我们解决剩下的保险措施啊
Thanks for taking off those last couple levels of security.
尼克早就给你装了窃听器
Nick had you wired.
原来在这
There it is.
别动 不准动
Don't move! Don't you move.
陷害我家人 是吧
Bring down my family. Huh?
还害我哥哥坐牢 你能逃得了吗 啊
You drag 'em through the gutter, then you think you're gonna get away with it?
宝贝 手铐
Babe, the cuffs.
会疼的呃
This might hurt.
退后 退到保险箱旁边
Back up. Back against the safe.
把自己铐在上面
Cuff yourself to it.
快点
Do it!
不知道哪种方式让我感觉更爽
I don't know what I'm going to enjoy more,
是杀了你们呢
having you killed,
还是看着你们两个过着可悲的生活
or watching you two suffer through your pathetic little lives.
无所谓
Whatever.
很高兴见到你 戴夫
It's good seeing you, Dave.
妮娜
Nina!
阿克曼
Ackerman!
我们两天后回来 你能帮我们保管一下吗
We'll be back in two days. Could you hold onto this for us?
- 当然没问题了 - 我叫卡西迪
- Of course, sir. - Name's Cassidy.
- 放心好了 卡西迪先生 - 谢谢你了
- You're all set, Mr. Cassidy. - Thank you.
- 你们玩的开心啊 - 你也是啊
- You folks have a great day. - You, too.
见了个鬼 怎么了
God damn it. What?
他弟弟和他女人把钻石抢走了
The brother and the girlfriend have the diamond!
他们他妈的就在酒店里
They're in the goddamned hotel!
天啊
Jesus.
卡西迪手上有引爆装置
Cassidy's got a bomb trigger.
把他解决了 准许开枪
Take him out. Kill shots.
- 是我 说吧 - 好 情况是这样的
- Yeah. Go. - Okay, so here's the deal.
卡西迪让我们去查沃克 他是个大坏蛋
Cassidy put us on to Walker. A very bad guy.
我们知道他有共犯 但突然发现那些人都死了
We knew he had accomplices and, suddenly, he turns up dead.
这样下来 就让我们的的案子有点难办了
Which, you know, sort of screwed up the case for us a bit.
我知道档案里有些什么 什么没在档案里
I know what's in the file, Evans. What's not in the file?
好吧 听着 想告上法庭这点证据是不够的
Okay, look. There wasn't enough for a courtroom,
不过我们内部有另外两名警察的间接证据
but internally we have strong circumstantial on two other cops.
他们是麦克·阿克曼和但丁·马库斯
A Michael Ackerman and a Dante Marcus.
他在那儿
That's him!
让开 追 追
Get out of the way! Go, go!
所有人都在为你担心 孩子 把这拿上 快走 快走
Everybody's pulling for you, kid! Take this! Go, go, go!
所有人都给我让开 快让开
Everyone, out of the way! Move!
他朝哪边跑了
Where did he go?
朝这边追
Go this way!
你没事吧
Are you all right?
乔伊·卡西迪吗
Joey Cassidy.
客房服务
Room service.
我没叫客房服务
I didn't order any room service.
- 你们呆着别动 - 趴下
- Just stay there! - Stay down!
趴下
Get down!
- 你没事吧 - 给我出去
- Are you okay? - Get out!
不准动 呆在这里
Don't move! Stay where you are!
趴下 趴下
Stay down! Stay down!
让我看看 我想看
Let me see! I wanna see!
噢 天哪
Oh, my God!
快看
Look!
那人在上面
The guy's up there!
不管你怎么反抗 总是殊途同归 流血 喘息 眼泪
It always ends the same, blood, snot and tears.
钻石在哪儿 难缠的家伙
Now where's the rock, tough guy?
你打起来像个娘们一样
You hit like a girl.
你哪儿来的 新泽西州
Where you from? Jersey?
我布朗克斯区的
I'm from the Bronx.
鲁兹 你一定要阻止特警队
Lutz, you need to call off tactical!
这儿没有炸弹引爆器 这儿连个屁都没有
There is no bomb trigger! We got jack shit here!
默瑟 这太疯狂了 我有命令在身
Mercer, this is nuts. I have orders.
给你的命令是错的
Your orders are wrong!
够了 够了
Okay! Okay!
- 他身上没枪 - 我身上没枪
- He's not armed! - I'm not armed!
- 手举起来 - 不准开枪 把枪放下
- Hands in the air! - Hold your fire! Guns down!
- 跪下 - 嘿 别激动
- Get down on your knees! - Hey, easy!
- 尼克 跪下 - 把手举起来
- Nick, get down. - But keep your hands in the air!
- 把枪放下 快点 - 跪下
- Drop your weapons! Come on, guys! - Down on your knees.
- 找到他了 抓到他了 - 跪下
- We got him! We got him! - Down on your knees!
把手举起来
Do not drop your hands!
- 把手举高了 - 好了 好了 我们抓住他
- Get your hands up! - Okay, okay. All right! We got it!
- 事态已经在我们控制之下了 - 默瑟 退下
- It's under control! - Mercer! Stand down.
- 一切在控制之下了 马库斯 - 我说了 退下
- It's under control, Marcus. - I said stand down!
- 我哪儿都不去 - 好吧
- I'm not going anywhere! - That's it.
上士 因阻挠办案逮捕她 立刻生效 执行命令
Sergeant, arrest her for obstruction. Right now, let's go.
- 你要逮捕我 - 带到下面指挥所去
- You gonna arrest me? - Take her down to command.
- 放开我 - 快点走
- Get off me. - Move your ass.
这他妈算是什么 你个混蛋
What the hell is this? You son of a bitch!
是啊 是啊 你打算怎么着
Yeah, yeah, okay. What are you gonna do?
线报说他安放了炸药 你带着人退回到第22层
We got intel he placed a bomb. I need you to get your guys back down to 22.
这里我来好了 你们走吧 集合 出发
I got this. Let's go. Saddle up! Let's go!
- 上面没人了 - 不要啊
- We're clear. - No.
不要 乔伊 乔伊
No! Joey! Joey!
- 我爱你 - 没事的 宝贝
- I love you. - It's gonna be okay, baby.
- 我爱你 我爱你 - 不 不要啊
- I love you. I love you. - No, no!
我有个消息要告诉你 伙计
I got news for you, pal.
恐怕是要有事了
This is not gonna be okay.
我早料到了
Yeah, I know.
我们这里算个总账吧 卡西迪先生
Here's where we're at, Mr. Cassidy.
你死定了
You're dead.
但只要你配合我们 就有机会和我们讨价还价
But your efforts have earned you the opportunity
放你家人一条生路
to negotiate for the lives of your family.
告诉我钻石在哪里 否则你弟弟就准备摔成烂泥吧
Tell me where the rock is or your little brother goes flying.
你死有余辜 但这小鬼 我会放他走的
You earned what you got coming. But the kid? I'll let him go.
- 这事和他一点关系都没有 - 钻石在哪儿
- It's got nothing to do with him! - Where is it?
- 把他推下去 - 等一下
- Throw him off! - Hold on!
你要干什么
What are you doing?
- 别给他 尼克 - 闭嘴
- Don't do it, Nick! - Shut up!
- 别给他 - 闭嘴
- Don't do it! - Shut up!
好极了
Impressive.
这世上有两种人
There's two kinds of people in this world.
一种人可以随心所欲做任何事情
People who will do anything to get what they want,
其他人都是废物
and everybody else.
你输了 尼克
You lose, Nick.
又输了
Again.
把这事情解决了
Clean this mess up.
给你10秒钟时间 尼克
You got 10 seconds, Nick.
就10秒钟 不然我就把你弟弟从这楼顶上扔下去
Ten, or I'm gonna throw your brother right off the roof.
嘿 伙计 她今天过得可不顺了 换做是我的话 我会照她说的做
Hey, buddy, she's had a pretty rough day. I'd do what she says.
条子们有钥匙 你个笨蛋
Cops have keys, you douche.
我不知道这样做对不对啊
I don't know that this is such a great idea.
你知道怎么着 你答应我今天来自杀的
You know what? You promised me a suicide today.
让楼下的人饱饱眼福吧 快点 尼克
Now give these people what they want. Come on, Nick.
他跟这事没任何关系 放了他
He had nothing to do with it! You leave him alone.
就剩5秒了
Now it's five!
这是你我之间的事情 你个人渣
It's between us, you piece of shit!
- 4秒 - 放他走
- Four! - Let him go!
- 快跳 - 我要扔了
- Jump! - I'm gonna do it.
麦克 你没事吧
Mike! Are you okay?
继续跑
Go on.
放松点
Take it easy.
听着 我对不起你 尼克
Look. I'm sorry, Nick.
我不知道他们要陷害你
I didn't know they were going to set you up.
我不想进监狱 我不是那种人 明白吗
I couldn't go to prison. I'm just not that guy, you know?
警员受伤 警员受伤
Officer down! Officer down!
顶楼请求立刻医疗支援
Request immediate assistance on the roof.
尼克 他要逃走了
Nick, he's getting away!
重复一遍 警员受伤 警员受伤
Repeat! Officer down! Officer down!
尼克
Nick!
对不起 尼克
I'm sorry, Nick.
嘿 天无绝人之路...
Hey, one way or another...
- 尼克 - 不要
- Nick! - No!
快点 伙计们 退后
Come on, folks! Stay back!
- 大卫 - 他在那儿
- David! - There he is!
上车
Let's go!
不许动 不许动
All right, freeze! Freeze!
现在你要怎么样呢 嗯
So what's it gonna be? Hmm?
就地正法 还是滚回监狱里去
A shot in the head? Or back to prison?
拍到没有
Are you getting that?
你以为你逃得掉
You thought you'd get away with this?
看到没 我是无辜的
See? I'm an innocent man!
- 钻石在他身上 - 我是无辜的
- He has the diamond! - I'm innocent!
我是无辜的
I'm innocent!
我爱你 伙计 我爱你
I love you, man! I love you!
你最好给我小心点
You got eyes in the back of your head?
这事我跟你没完
'Cause I'm not through with you, pal.
他们会在监狱好好爱护你的
Yeah, they're gonna love you in prison.
卡西迪先生 今天你证明了自己的清白 现在你感觉如何
Mr. Cassidy, you've proven that you're innocent. How do you feel today?
今天够呛的 是吧
Crazy day, huh?
但是我很荣幸再次和你一起工作
But I would be proud to work with you again.
你做的不错呃
You did good out there.
谢谢你 多尔蒂
Thanks, Dougherty.
似乎州长来过了
Looks like the Governor came through.
留下时间给你们告别一下
I'll let you two say your goodbyes.
待会见 多尔蒂
See you around, Dougherty.
释放一名囚犯
One coming out.
- 你没事吧 - 没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
我们走吧
Let's get you out of here.
我想我们还是从后面走吧 一堆记者守在门口呢
I figured I'd walk you out the back. There's like a million reporters.
既然你已经出来了 就没什么想跟我说的吗
Now that you're off the ledge, you got nothing to say to me?
- 说吧 - 说什么
- Spill it. - What?
"说什么?" 你怎么拿到钻石的呢
"What?" How'd you get the diamond?
我们到安静的地方慢慢说
Let's go someplace quiet.
没错 丹 今天上演窗台惊魂的尼克·卡西迪
That's right, Dan. It has been confirmed that the man on the ledge, Nick Cassidy,
前警官无罪释放
已经被证实释放出狱
has been released from custody.
前警官无罪释放
卡西迪万岁
It's Cassidy!
坐了两年牢
Two years in.
我们都出名了
Don't I know it.
嘿 酒保 换台吧 这堆废话我听厌了
Bartender! Change the channel. I'm sick of this jackass.
恐怕不行啊 我可喜欢这个台了
Afraid not. That's my favorite channel.
莉迪亚
Lydia,
这是我爸爸
meet my dad.
你爸爸
Your dad?
我叫弗兰克·卡西迪
Frank Cassidy.
您还活得好好的啊
Alive and well.
很高兴再见到你
Pleasure to meet you. Again.
开什么玩笑
You gotta be shitting me.
你竟然是他爸爸
You're his father.
快走开
Get off now.
我为你自豪
I'm so proud of you.
放开我老婆
Get your hands off my wife.
- 是女朋友 - 只是女朋友
- Girlfriend. - Girlfriend.
等我一下
Hold on a second.
嘿 大伙安静一下 安静一下
Everyone, quiet down. Just quiet down.
安静
Quiet!
安吉拉·玛丽亚·洛佩斯
Angela Maria Lopez.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
- 一百个愿意 - 是吗
- Hell, yes. - Yeah?
让我看看 让我看看
Let me see it. Let me see it.
戴上试试 戴上试试
Try it on. Try it on.
我猜这是你们的传家宝吧
I'm gonna assume that's a family heirloom.
现在是了
It is now.
大家喝起来吧
Drinks all around!
- 喜欢吗 - 喜欢
- Do you like it? - Yeah!
阿斯各·莱斯
导 演
♪ Well, I'm running Police on my back ♪
♪ I've been hiding Police on my back ♪
巴勃罗·F·芬尼维斯
编 剧
♪ There was a shooting Police on my back ♪
洛伦佐·迪·博纳文图拉
马克·瓦赫拉迪安
制片人
♪ And the victim Well, he won't come back ♪
杰克·迈尔斯
戴维·雷迪
执行制片人
♪ I been running Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday ♪
保罗·卡梅伦
摄影指导
♪ Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday ♪
亚力克·哈蒙德
艺术指导
♪ Running Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday ♪
凯文·斯帝特
剪 辑
♪ Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday ♪
李察·基德
视觉特效
♪ What have I done? ♪
苏珊·莱尔
服装设计
♪ What have I done? ♪
亨利·杰克曼
配 乐
♪ Yes, I'm running down the railway track ♪
顶峰娱乐公司
荣誉出品
博纳文图拉影业
倾情制作
♪ Could you help me? Police on my back ♪
萨姆·沃辛顿
♪ They will catch me if I dare drop back ♪
♪ Won't you give me all the speed I lack? ♪
窗台上的男人
♪ I been running Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday ♪
伊丽莎白·班克斯
♪ Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday ♪
杰米·贝尔
♪ Running Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday ♪
安东尼·麦凯
♪ Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday ♪
爱德华·伯恩斯
提图斯·维里沃
♪ What have I done? ♪
珍尼希斯·罗德里格兹
凯拉·塞吉维克
艾德·哈里斯
♪ 'Cause I'm running ♪
迪布拉·阿奎拉 & 崔西亚·伍德
朱莉·塔克 & 罗斯·迈耶森
剪 辑